Mark Joseph Aspe

Web Developer



in mark-joseph-aspe

Skills

Front-End Web Development: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap & JavaScript

Back-End Web Development: MongoDB, ExpressJS & NodeJS

Full-Stack Web Development: MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS & NodeJS

Content Management System: Wordpress

Education

Postgraduate - Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp,

Zuitt Learning Institute Incorporated 08/2022 - 11/2022 | Quezon City, Philippines

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology - 4th yr. Undergraduate, Technological Institute of the Philippines 2010 - 2014 | Quezon City, Philippines

Certificates

- Front End Development ☑
- Back-End Development ☑
- Full Stack Development ☑
- Intensive I.T. Coding Bootcamp ☑

Profile

I am a Web Developer with experience building websites & web applications. Technologies I used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS and NodeJS. I also have experience working with Wordpress Development.

Take a look at my work or get in touch! https://mkpogs.github.io/mk-portfolio/ ☑

Professional Experience

ADJUDICATOR (SG8),

Philippine Health Insurance Corporation 08/2018 – 03/2023 | Pasig City, Philippines

- Reviews & verifies completeness and accuracy of forms and attached documents for Facility/Hospital Claims.
- Checks for deficiencies and corrects any incompatibilities while ensuring data integrity and security policies are followed.
- Provide assistance with other office tasks as required and ensures proper use of office management while addressing any malfunctions.

TS/X STEEL DETAILER,

Zoe Detailing International Inc. 08/2014 – 02/2018 | Pasig City, Philippines

- Prepares detailed drawings for structural and architectural design standards using SDS/2 and Tekla structures.
- · Prepares approval and construction drawings for steel erection plans, elevations, details, and sections in compliance with the company's drafting standards
- Creates 3D models of beams, columns, handrails, and other steel structures while maintaining paper-based filing and organizing systems, as well as computer maintenance and file backups.

IT Intern, Fusion BPO Services Phil. Inc. 11/2013 - 02/2014 | Pasig City, Philippines

- Responsible for the troubleshooting, testing, repairing, assembly and disassembly of computers.
- Network monitoring and updating MySQL Server database.